

ARMAN GOLCHOUBIAN

UI/UX Designer

(+98) 935 933 7840

golchoubian.design@gmail.com

Profile

I'm a Graphic & UI/UX Designer with a strong background and experience in different areas including UI/UX design, motion graphics & Visual design.

Designer focused on building brands and creating digital experiences.

Fascinated by technology, branding, and innovation and the impact that design has on each one.

★ Skills

Design

Research

Persona/Storyboard

User storie/ User journey/ User Flow

Wireframe

Prototype

Web Responsive Design

Storyboarding

Interaction Design

Visual Design

Web Design

iOS, Android Design

A/B Testing

Usability Test

Contextual Research

Agile/Scrum and Jira & Confluence

HTML/CSS

Software

Figma

Adobe XD

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe InDesign

Adobe After Effects

Adobe Premiere

Cinema 4D

Jira Software

Language

Persian English

Certification

Google UX Design Agile with Atlassian Jira

Portfolio

www.golchoubian.com/ www.linkedin.com/in/golchoubian www.dribbble.com/golchoubian

Experience

Mazinoor Factory

May 2019 - Up to the present

Senior UI/UX Designer

Leading luminaire manufacturer in the Iran, with over 40 years of experience. There is a great need to for design in Mazinoor various platforms as it deals with a wide range of individuals including customers, agents, architects and retailers.

- I always try to help the brand and it's sub-brands by doing research, A/B testing, Usability Test, web & application design and interaction design.
- Designing materials for online promotions for social media latforms, keeping brand guidelines in mind
- Designing user interfaces & user experiences, advertisement videos, motion graphics, catalogs, banners, posters, product packaging.

Mehraz Andishan Architecture

Sep 2017 - May 2018

Senior UI/UX Designer

- Helped conceptualize, design and develop digital and social communications to be utilized across all channels
- Interacted with Creative Directors, Account Leads, Art Directors and Copywriters to develop creative concepts and assist in the execution of ideas through design
- Led brainstorming sessions and design reviews
- Served as a key player in agency's evolving workflow process

Yalit Families Fitting

Nov 2016 - Sep 2017

UI/UX Designer

- Used diverse inputs to identify and define exciting new concepts, opportunities, and customer problems
- Developed creative concepts and implementations that are consistently on target with brand objectives
- Built solid understanding of the market and brand dynamics of assigned client projects

Freelance graphic design

Jun 2012 - May 2019

Graphic & UI/UX Designer - Motion Designer

- Designed engaging content in support of product needs and marketing initiatives
- Created layered files and print and web production ready files
- Collaborated with cross-functional design, development, and business teams to ensure all aspects of user experience have been thought through and optimized

Education

Emam Sadegh University

2006 - 2008

Associate's degree Computer Software